hello friend welcome to simple trade
this is Phil initial we are not
recommending any instructor by yourself
in this video number of strategies is
three this is continue of second first
video
if you're not watch the first studio
just go through the first Studio
start number one board upload dividend
ICICI Lombard gender Insurance Company
Limited share
549 52 Weeki 1547 52 week low 1070 phase
a little piston market cap large cap
different for rupees 50 paise recorded
28 October next day 27 October
second stock board approach dividend
Global education limited share price 450
52 Weeki 450 52 week long 39 rupees
Facebook
many stocks or skills are different one
rupees 50 recorded 26 November X date 24
November maybe it is 24 November
upcoming board meeting May consider dude
and please note may consider there is no
any guarantee but most of the case they
will declare mmu Limited
dividend record it will be 29 21st
November
thanks for watching